<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Cheungs - News</title>
  <updated>2021-01-19T10:23:14-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Cheungs</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/rising-ocean-freight-costs</id>
    <published>2021-01-19T10:23:14-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-19T11:34:48-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/rising-ocean-freight-costs"/>
    <title>Rising Ocean Freight Costs</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">Here at Cheungs we import from different countries for our offerings. Over the years we have seen costs move and adjust with the times, everything within reason. As with many things in 2020, these costs went a little crazy to say the least.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"><strong>Alright, what's the damage?</strong></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true" id="izf5ln-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2">Overseas shipping costs have effectively doubled within the last 8 months. This applies to any and every industry that imports goods from overseas whether it is a finished product, or general supplies. Every importer is feeling the pain right now.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="default" draggable="true" id="iq386k-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true" id="iqr42p-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2"><b data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true" id="iwn8us-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2">What impact is this having? </b></div>
<div data-gjs-type="default" draggable="true" id="ilejzi-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true" id="iwtruc-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2">In short, importers are trying to find solutions to mitigate the cascading increase in costs from shipping alone. Because of the lengthy summer lockdowns, businesses had put a hold on re-stocks and shipping which created a lull. Closer to the end of 2020, everyone rushed to get merchandise in to be available for the holidays. That rush had overloaded ports all over the Pacific Ocean including West Coast ports in the US and we are still feeling the effects right now.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="default" draggable="true" id="it1x3h-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true" id="ilynai-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2-2">After speaking with our shipping industry contacts, we expect these increases to continue to go up at least until the Summer. For many industries in the US this may mean a continued lack of inventory, cost increases and lengthened restock timelines as response options to the situation.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"><strong>What do you recommend?</strong></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">﻿This situation will affect different industries in a variety of ways. We definitely recommend planning out re-orders for product, from any of your suppliers, further in advance. Especially for holiday specific needs such as Christmas, planning ahead this year will ensure inventory stability. In addition, if you utilize any supplies such as shipping or craft materials, we recommend double checking lead times and costs as the year progresses. Some of your vendors may import these items from overseas. Double checking with your suppliers as they navigate this shock price increase, especially leading up to peak holidays, will help keep you ready and flexible.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">
<strong></strong><strong>What about Cheungs?</strong>
</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">Our current plan is to stay the course. We will not be raising costs in response to this situation. 2021 is going to be a very tight year as our communities trudge through the road of recovery, but any increase we make will negatively affect you, our retail partners. In addition, we will work hard to keep our items in stock and prepare holiday-specific pieces well in advance to meet your needs.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">While we hope this situation will improve soon, the future is largely unknown. For the time being we will tighten our belts a little more and hang in there!</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">For many of you reading this, your experiences will vary. Some of you may be aware of this situation all too well while others may be hearing about these cost explosions for the first time. No matter which group you are in, I hope this information helps you have a more informed mindset to better tackle 2021.</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">Thank you all for your continued partnership and I hope you are able to take some time to relax and enjoy a cool beer!</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">Spencer Cheung II</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true">P.S. Got a question or want to continue the conversation? Shoot us an email at info@cheungs.com with your thoughts!</div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>
<div data-gjs-type="text" draggable="true"></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/2020s-trade-shows-know-what-to-expect</id>
    <published>2020-07-07T21:49:13-07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-07-07T21:50:05-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/2020s-trade-shows-know-what-to-expect"/>
    <title>2020&apos;s Trade Shows - Know what to expect!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Hey there!</p>
<p>With the 2020 trade shows just over a month away we wanted to give you some stock knowledge so that you are better prepared and know what to expect.</p>
<p>In short, each trade show location has been constantly preparing and trialing new  procedures to protect the health and safety of all attendees. </p>
<p>Our team is confident in the new safety measure and we will proudly be opening our show rooms at our 3 spaces across the country! To learn more about the safety information we have consolidated, click <a href="https://cheungs.com/pages/2020-trade-show-tips-info"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>here.</strong></span></a></p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"></span>Thank you and we hope to see you soon!</p>
<p>Spencer Cheung II</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/we-are-now-open</id>
    <published>2020-05-14T21:03:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-14T21:06:06-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/we-are-now-open"/>
    <title>We are now open!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We are happy to announce we are now open regularly. To all of our partners, we are able to receive and process orders and any restocks you need. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>For our local friends, we have implemented new guidelines and rules for in-person visits and pickups. Please read the following carefully:</p>
<p>- We ask that only staff enter and exit the office area</p>
<p>- Showroom walk-throughs are available through a separate entrance and while maintaining social distancing</p>
<p>- Pickups are available! Call or order ahead and await your items in our parking lot, we will bring them to you</p>
<p>- Masks must be warn at all times for any interaction with Cheungs team members</p>
<p>- On site facilities such as restrooms are not open to the public (Sorry!)</p>
<p> - For in-person service, just knock on our window! We'll be right out to help you</p>
<p>We are proud to continue serving all of our partners as they gear towards opening back up. If you have any questions or concerns, please give us a call or email us.</p>
<div style="text-align: center;">
<div><strong>714-549-9080</strong></div>
<div><strong>info@cheungs.com</strong></div>
<div><strong></strong></div>
<div style="text-align: left;">Thank you,</div>
<div style="text-align: left;">Spencer Cheung II</div>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/we-are-working-from-home</id>
    <published>2020-03-23T11:58:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-03-23T11:58:47-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/we-are-working-from-home"/>
    <title>We are working from home!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>On March 19th, California's Governor Gavin Newsom issued an order for Californians to stay in doors unless conducting essential activities. After speaking to medical professionals and taking guidance from our local government, we decided to temporarily suspend our services and close our main office.</p>
<p>Our goal is to join the greater movement to save lives, ease the burden on first responders and medical professionals, and protect the long term growth of our local and global communities. </p>
<p>Because of this decision we are unable to process any new orders at this time. Despite this, we remain ready to take in any scheduled or restock orders. Once we open we will process them swiftly and with the same level of service and trust you know us for.</p>
<p>Currently we do not know when the Governor will lift or amend this order so we are tentatively closed until the end of March. Come April, we will seek out further guidance from our local officials and provide updates on when we can open again.</p>
<p>If you have any questions regarding existing orders or wish to contact us about scheduling a future order, please email us at <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>info@cheungs.com</strong></span>.</p>
<p>Our family has been and will continue to be here to serve you and take care of your needs. To all of our partners and friends, we remain humbled and thankful for your continued business and trust.</p>
<p>Thank you,</p>
<p>Spencer Cheung II</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/create-inspired-living-spaces-with-new-styles</id>
    <published>2020-01-07T11:15:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-01-07T11:38:32-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/create-inspired-living-spaces-with-new-styles"/>
    <title>Create Inspired Living Spaces with New Styles!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Shake off the cold and visit us this trade show season! We will be heading to our three locations with the newest styles in tow and are already hard at work preparing our showrooms for you.</p>
<p>Unable to attend? Not a problem! Our <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><a href="https://cheungs.com/collections/new-styles">newest items</a></span> are live on site with stock rolling in throughout the month. Just visit the New Styles tab or click <a href="https://cheungs.com/collections/new-styles"><span style="text-decoration: underline;">here.</span></a></p>
<p>We hope you will be able to attend as we love meeting familiar faces and creating new partnerships! If you would like to create an appointment for undivided attention give us a holler by calling 714-549-9080 or by emailing info@cheungs.com.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><u><strong>Our Schedule:</strong></u></p>
<p><br><strong>Dallas Market Center </strong><span>in Dallas, Texas - Space: 2F125</span><br><span>     When: January 8th to January 14th</span><br><strong>Americas Mart </strong><span>in Atlanta, Georgia - Building 1 - Space: 19A9 to 19A11</span><br><span>     When: January 14th - January 21st</span><br><strong>Las Vegas Market Center </strong><span>in Las Vegas, Nevada - Buidling C - Space: C952</span><br><span>     When: January 26th to January 30th</span></p>
<p><span>Thank you,</span></p>
<p><span>The Cheungs Team</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/cheungs-and-the-trade-war</id>
    <published>2019-09-12T17:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2019-09-13T15:19:44-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/cheungs-and-the-trade-war"/>
    <title>Cheungs and the Trade War</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[Dear Friends and Longtime Partners,<br><br>As many of you have seen on the news, United States tariffs on Chinese goods will increase or will be placed on goods previously not under the tariffs. In short, this is what will happen:<br><br>- Roughly half of all goods from China currently with tariffs of 25% will increase to 30% by October 15<br><br>- The remaining goods being imported from China will incur a tariff of 15% by 2019 end, a portion starting in November<br><br>- Tariffs will continue to be paid by United States importers such as ourselves, Cheungs<br><br>Across the country businesses both large and small are working diligently to find a response to the effects of the current trade war ranging from moving production to increasing prices.<br><br><strong>What actions will we take?</strong><br><br>Our plan will be simple. We plan on maintaining all prices on our products just as we have since the start of the Trade War and will not apply any increases to offset the tariffs. We understand that pricing is the key factor more than ever and our goal is to endure the brunt of the effects so that your business can continue to operate smoothly especially with the upcoming holiday season.<br><br>Our hope is that an agreement will be reached which will see these tariffs reduced back to their Pre-Trade War levels. Until then our team will continue to work harder than ever to provide you the best service we can.<br><br>If you have any questions about our company, our plan or about how the tariffs are affecting us, please feel to write, call or stop by in person. We remain deeply appreciative of the partnerships you all have given us and look forward to what the future will bring.<br><br>Thank you,<br>The Cheungs Team]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/summer-trade-show-and-new-styles</id>
    <published>2019-05-21T16:13:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-21T16:28:17-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/summer-trade-show-and-new-styles"/>
    <title>Summer Trade Show and New Styles</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>With the beautiful sunshine and the season of Summer comes a new round of trade show visits and brand new styles! We are happy to announce we will again be showcasing our entire line in Dallas, Atlanta and Las Vegas. For complete details just look below!</p>
<p><strong>Summer 2019</strong></p>
<p><strong>June 19th to June 25th</strong></p>
<p><span>Dallas Market Center  at the Plaza </span><span>-</span><strong> </strong><span>Space: 2F125</span></p>
<p><strong>July 9th to July 15th</strong></p>
<p><span>Americas Mart </span><span>- </span><span>Building 1 - 19A9-19A11</span></p>
<p><strong>July 28th to August 1st</strong></p>
<p><span>Las Vegas Market Center</span><strong><span> </span>- </strong><span>Building C - C952</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>Our team has been working hard on gathering and preparing stylishly new designs over the last few months. Stay tuned in the coming days for sneak peeks as we edge closer to our first trade show in Dallas!</span></p>
<p><span>As always, if you have any questions feel free to call us at 714-549-9080 or email us at info.cheungsrattan@gmail.com.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>Thank you,</span></p>
<p><span>Spencer C</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/2019-trade-shows-and-new-items</id>
    <published>2019-01-22T10:11:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2019-01-22T10:25:38-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/2019-trade-shows-and-new-items"/>
    <title>2019 Trade Shows and New Items</title>
    <author>
      <name>Christiane Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>January is a time for new! With our trade shows fully underway, our newest pieces are on display and ready to be viewed. From farm fresh styles to contemporary decor, there is sure to be a stylishly functional additional for everyone.</p>
<p>To view these new items, visit our "New Styles" section or click <span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #76a5af;"><strong><a href="https://cheungs.com/collections/new-styles" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="color: #76a5af; text-decoration: underline;">here</a></strong></span> and place your order today!</p>
<p>As always, if you have any questions please drop us a line at 714-549-9080 or email us at info.cheungsrattan@gmail.com</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Cheers!</p>
<p>Spencer C</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/trade-show-shipping-is-underway</id>
    <published>2018-08-22T00:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-08-22T10:44:51-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/trade-show-shipping-is-underway"/>
    <title>Trade Show Shipping Is Underway!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Our team has begun shipping out all of our trade show orders! Give us a call or email if you need assistance or want to make a change.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/trade-show-shipping-is-underway">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Our team here is hard at working preparing, finalizing and shipping your trade show orders. We have already started reaching out to confirm final details and hope everything will be exactly as you need it! Curious for more info? See below!</p>
<p><strong>What if I have not been contacted yet?</strong></p>
<p>We are going through our orders as quickly as possible and take into account your requested ship date. Once we have everything ready we will give you a call! </p>
<p><strong>I need to make a change to my order!</strong></p>
<p>Want to add, cancel or alter an existing quantity or change the ship date? Give us a call at 714-549-9080! We will get your requests written down immediately.</p>
<p><strong>How about a special something to brighten up my day?</strong></p>
<p>Our dedicated, canine morale boosting team will gladly be up for the challenge. Just let us know and we will send you today's special picture! </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/online-ordering-now-available</id>
    <published>2018-05-29T10:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-05-29T10:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/online-ordering-now-available"/>
    <title>Online Ordering Now Available!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We are happy to announce that our website is ready to accept online orders for our wholesale partners. Simply add it to your cart and checkout! To view a full step by step guide please click <a href="https://cheungs.com/pages/placing-an-order" target="_blank" title="How to place an order" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<p>If you need any assistance or have additional questions regarding shipping, bulk pricing and packaging, please feel free to call us at 714-549-9080.</p>
<p>Thanks!</p>
<p>The Cheungs Team</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/cheungs-winter-trade-show-season</id>
    <published>2018-01-20T13:09:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-01-20T13:15:47-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://cheungs.com/blogs/news/cheungs-winter-trade-show-season"/>
    <title>Cheungs Winter Trade Show Season!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Spencer Cheung</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Our team is well underway with our biannual trade show season tour around the country. We invite you to join us at any of our three locations to get a first hand look at what new pieces and finishes we will be offering this year!</p>
<p>If you are new to trade shows and have never attended one, we feature show-only specials that are offered on location while the trade show provides a great medium for us to get to meet you and learn more about how we can add value to your business. </p>
<p>We are currently hard at work in Dallas, Texas at the Dallas Market Center, so if you are in the neighborhood please drop by! If you are unable to make it we will have one last stop at the end of the month in Las Vegas, Nevada. For additional information about our trade shows click or tap the link below.</p>
<p><a href="https://cheungs.com/pages/upcoming-trade-show-dates" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">More Info!</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Until next time,</p>
<p>The Cheungs Team</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
